你还好吗*
*What's the matter?
你最近还好吗*
*What's the matter with you lately?
你还好吗*
*What's the matter?
你最近还好吗*
*What's the matter with you lately?
你的爱一直不能让我满足*
*Oh, your love is never good enough.
你的爱已经不能打动我的心*
*Oh, your love is lost on me?
其他地方都没问题
Rest of the place is clear.
嗯  这家伙身上没有任何证件
Yeah. Uh...no I.D. on this one.
也不清楚墙上是谁的血
And no clue who is painted on the walls.
看来不管发生了什么  咱们错过了
Well, whatever happened, looks like we missed it.
是的  真好
Yeah. Great.
等下
Wait a second.
什么玩意儿
What the hell?
本不该是这样的结局
凶鬼恶灵
第八季 第四集
咬 殇
本不该是这样的结局
喂  大导演
Hey, Christopher Nolan.
-怎么了  -镜头盖没开
- Yeah? - Lens cap.
见鬼  该死的
Oh, crap. Damn.
干得好  天才
Strong work, genius.
老兄  我不知道该拍什么内容
Dude, I have no idea what to make this movie about.
我可是视听俱乐部主席
And I'm, like -- I'm A/V club president,
所以  必须得拍好
so, you know, it's got to be good.
来  给我
Here. Give me that.
我来告诉你拍什么
I'll tell you what you're gonna make it about.
你来拍  好啊
You're gonna make it? Okay.
在这个表里不一的世界
In a world where nothing is what it seems...
一个年轻帅气勇敢的纯爷们
...one brave, shockingly handsome, virile young man
和他那忠诚
and his faithful,
-但却学习无能的机器人男仆  -少来
- learning-disabled, robotic manservant... - Oh, no.
必须与一波又一波机器蠢蛋作战
...must battle through waves of cybernetic asshats
以给女性带来性解放...
in order to sexually liberate the women of --
行了  给我  给我
Okay. Give me that. Give me that.
拜托
Oh, please.
我打赌她们中至少有一个愿意拿你来
I bet at least one of these girls would let you partake
练习跟男生玩暧昧
in their awkward-guy experimental phase.
什么  这些女孩儿
What? These girls?
得了吧  不是废物
Yep. Okay. Hashtag fails.
就是怪咖
Homeschooled.
还有没出柜的拉拉
Secretly in love with her roommates.
听乡村音乐的小女生
Listens to country music.
老兄  老兄  12点方向那个金发妞儿
Oh, dude, dude. 12:00, blonde.
-正点  -等等  她是不是  糟了
- Yeah. - Wait. Is she -- oh, crap, crap.
-老兄  拿着  快拿着  -我不想拿
- Dude, take it, take it. Just take it. - I don't want to take it.
刚刚你们在拍我吗
Were you just filming me?
没有啊  我才不会
No. Uh, I wouldn't do that.
你们的装了新固件吗
Does it have the new firmware?
嗯  有的  有的
Uh, yes. Yes, it does.
运行怎么样
How's it handle?
你来试试
You tell me.
你们的设置完全不对
Well, your settings are way off.
我喜欢这种色彩
Oh, I-I like the way the colors --
你大概不会关心的
You probably don't care about that.
那你刚刚不是在打量我吗
Yeah, so, you weren't checking me out?
我确实喜欢注重隐私的美女
Well, I do have a thing for beautiful women who respect their privacy.
抱歉  我净说傻话
Uh, dick move on my part. I'm sorry.
没关系
Don't be.
我喜欢有超赞摄像机的男生
I have a thing for guys with cool cameras.
不不不  这电影是很不错
No, no, no. Look, it's a great movie,
只是比起来  我更喜欢《去年在马里昂巴德》
but of the two, I-I prefer "Last year at Marienbad."
你知道吗
You know?
是啊  很经典
Yeah. It's a classic.
是啊  你觉得镜头怎样
Yeah. How do you like that lens?
不错啊  轻多了
It's good. Yeah, yeah. It's lighter for sure.
挺好
It's good.
你知道吧  迈克尔对摄像机一窍不通
You know, uh, Michael knows nothing about cameras, right?
知道  但我在教他
Yeah. But, uh, I'm teaching him.
教谁
Teaching who?
我的男友
Oh, my boyfriend.
他高大帅气
He's, uh, big, tall, and handsome.
听起来很招人啊
Mm. Sounds delish.
是啊  你们应该见一面
Yeah, you should totally meet him.
是吗
Yeah?
让我想想  五年以后
Let's see. Five years from now?
希望能够通过律师资格考试  做个律师
Hopefully passed the bar exam, practicing law.
不去大公司干  而是...
Nothing corporate, something, uh...
环保事业之类的
Something green, you know?
做环保  很好啊
Green is good.
嬉皮士
Hippie.
嬉皮士反对大企业  倡导和平  亲近自然
你闭嘴
Oh, shut up.
天呐
Oh, geez.
或许去HBO工作
Uh, maybe, like, working for HBO
或者像迈克尔・摩尔那样
or -- or, like, Michael Moore.
迈克尔・摩尔  美国著名纪录片导演  创作方向多为社会时事题材
那样不错
That'd be cool.
你更嬉皮
Double hippie.
随便啦
Whatever.
我要乘船在海上航行
I will be on a boat in the middle of the ocean
我美丽的女友也会伴我左右
with my beautiful girl by my side.
你个傻瓜
Aww...sap.
你也可以一起来
And you can come, too.
好啊  真会说话
Nice. See what you just did there?
...的展示
...display of that,
下次我们先把手举起来
let's make sure we put our hand up first next time.
好了  机灵鬼们  拿出笔来
All right, brains, let's get our pens and pencils out.
该记笔记了
It's time for notes.
我们来看看被戏谑地称为猪仔的小朋友
So, let's turn our attention to our cruelly nicknamed friend Piggy.
他用他的眼镜生火  做日晷
He uses his glasses to create fire, the sun dial.
《蝇王》[诺贝尔文学奖获得者威廉・高丁寓言体小说]
一年级英语文学
他还很理性
He's also rational.
他在小岛上运用了理性的思考
He inhabits rational thought on the island.
我错过什么了
What'd I miss?
一堂鲁德斯基教授完美的课罢了
Just another pitch-perfect lecture from Professor Ludensky.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道赛门其实代表了耶稣吗
Do you know Simon was a Christ figure?
赛门  猪仔  雷尔夫都是《蝇王》中的人物
知道
Yeah.
不知道
No.
你都拍下来了吧
Please tell me you taped it.
拜托  谁最爱你
Come on. Who loves you?
我怎么离得开你
Aww. I wish I could quit you.
你就逗我吧
Yeah, right. Yeah.
看着点儿  傻逼
Oh, hey. Watch it, asshat!
你刚刚叫我什么
What'd you call me?
行了  走吧  我想去看看
Come on. Let's move. I want to see it.
走吧
Let's go.
可恶
Oh, man.
你能拍点这个吗  我电影用
Hey, can you shoot some of this for my movie?
-合法吗  -谁管呢
- Is that legal? - Who cares?
情况不妙啊
Yeah, that's not good.
有人在校园里被杀吗
Someone got murdered on campus?
你们俩的公寓离这儿很近啊
You guys live two blocks from here.
瞧啊  警界双雄
Look, look, look. Starsky and Hutch.
妙女神探
Rizzoli and Isles.
我是罗斯特工  这位是哈德森特工
Special agent Rose, and this is special agent Hudson.
你们怎么会来
What the hell are you guys doing here?
工作  能不能说说怎么回事
Our jobs. You want to tell us what's going on?
听你的  老大
Whatever you say, boss.
住楼上的女人打电话
Got a call from a woman that lives upstairs.
说她听到了打斗声
said, uh, she heard an attack,
下楼就看见邻居死在这里
came down, found her neighbor here.
叫雅各布・卡特
Jacob Carter.
-他说谁  -雅各布・卡特
- Who'd he say? - Uh, Jacob Carter?
-没听清楚  -目击者还在家吗
- I don't know. - Well, is the witness still home?
当然在  她不算特别可信
Sure is. She's not the most reliable type.
说她听见了嚎叫声
She said she heard some kind of growl,
像是有郊狼
like there was a coyote down here.
太棒了
Awesome.
联调局的人来了
So, the FBI is here.
你的邻居被杀了  你完全淡定吗
Your neighbor got murdered, but you're totally cool.
不是淡定
No. It's not -- it's not that I'm cool.
只是...我是说
It's just that, like...I mean,
联调局派人来是好事吧
that it's good that the FBI are here, right?
这么有逻辑  太烦人了
That -- that is so annoyingly logical.
喂  宝贝儿  听
Hey, baby. Listen.
很好听  什么歌
Oh. It's pretty. What is it?
我们第一次见面时放的歌
It's the song that was playing when we first met.
你真是好得过分
Aww. You are so disgustingly sweet.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- You ready? - Yeah.
-好  我得走了  -什么
- Cool. I got to go. - What?
你用我们的歌铺垫好气氛
So, you just foam the runway with our song
然后就这么走了
and then you got to head out the door?
我答应帮他测试新摄像机
I promised I'd help him test the new cameras.
别来这套
Don't give me that crap.
我知道你们两个白痴
I know you two idiots
要为《蠢蛋搞怪秀》拍视频片段
are gonna go shoot cut scenes for "Jackass."
别这样
Come on.
你也知道他没别人作伴  我们改天
We both know he has nobody else to do this with. Rain check.
随便  我不管了
Whatever. You're dead to me.
摆个酷
Do something cool.
伙计  这棵树真棒
Dude, this tree is awesome.
说不定我能来个倒挂
Maybe I could -- maybe I could...get upside down and --
不  我让你摆酷
No, no, I said cool.
这蠢死了
This is stupid.
拍到了吗  看得到我吗
Can you get -- can you see me?
我要...这样酷不
Gonna try and get -- is this cool?
伙计  感觉太棒了
'cause, man, it feels pretty cool.
简直就是《阿呆与阿瓜3》
It's like "Dumb & Dumber 3."
-等等  伙计  -怎么了
- Wait, dude, dude, dude, dude. - What?
-回头  回头  -什么
- Turn around. Turn around. - What?
-回头  是那两个联调局的  -什么
- Turn. It's those FBI guys. - What?
帮我下去  帮我从树上下去
Help -- help me down this tree. Help me out of the tree.
好的
Oh, all right.
多谢你们的配合
Well, thank you, guys, very much for your help.
你们可以走了
You're free to go.
好了  这里没有案子
All right. There is not a case.
有案子  是你迟钝了
There is a case here. You're rusty.
我们得再查查  走吧
We just got to dig a little deeper. Come on.
伙计  不可思议
Dude, it's so crazy.
是我想多了
Is it just me or are you getting
还是这两位搭档基情荡漾啊
a workplace-romance vibe from those two?
我们走
Let's go.
过来  快看啊
Come here, come here. Look, look.
蠢货打野炮
D-bags mating in the wild.
好  走
Okay, go, go.
停下
Stop.
Stop!
三振出局  蠢货
Strike three. You're a dick.
你怎么回事
What's your problem?
传到YouTube上一定火爆了
This is gonna look great on YouTube.
-该死  -该死
- Oh. Oh, crap. - Oh, crap.
喂  搞什么
Hey! What the hell?!
-死了死了  -天呐
- Oh, crap, crap. - Oh, God.
布莱恩  布莱恩
Hey, Brian, Brian!
去斯考特妈妈家找我
Meet me at Scott's mother's house!
天呐
Oh, God.
别这样  我可是给了她钱的
Oh, come on. I paid her fair and square, man!
谢谢你  布莱恩  今晚真开心
Thanks for a great night out, Bri.
谁在那儿
Hello?
有人吗
斯考特  别闹了
Scott, cut it out, man!
天呐
Oh, God.
上帝啊
迈克尔  出来吧  伙计
Hey, Michael. You can come out now, dude.
斯考特找了我们一阵就走了
Scott looked for us for a while but bailed.
迈克
Mike?
迈克  老兄
Mike? Dude.
我的上帝啊
Oh, my God. Dude.
迈克尔  你没事吧
Michael. You okay, man?
我没事
I'm okay.
发生什么事
What happened?
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
凯特
Kate!
我的天呐  宝贝  宝贝
Oh, my God! Baby, baby, baby, baby!
迈克尔被咬伤了
Something bit Michael.
-我的老天  -严重吗
- Oh, my god. - What is it? Is it bad?
-布莱恩  -凯特
- Brian. - Kate.
严重吗
Is it bad?
伤口...伤口消失了
The bite -- the bite's gone.
这里是911  您有什么紧急情况
911. What's your emergency?
你们两个混蛋是不是骗我
Did -- did you dicks just punk me?
什么  完全消失了
What? It's completely gone.
宝贝  没事了
Baby, it's okay.
亲爱的  没事了
Hey, hey, hey. Honey, it's okay.
没事了  宝贝
It's okay. Babe.
医生说他会没事的
The doctor said he's gonna be fine.
你听到了
You heard him.
他身上一点伤痕都没有
Literally not a scratch on the kid.
要是迈克尔出了什么事
If anything happens to Michael,
我真不知该怎么办
I-I don't know what I would do.
没事了
Shh. It's okay.
你把门扯下来了
Did you just pull that off?
好了  好了  现在换单手
Okay. Okay, okay. Now -- now one-handed.
我的老天
Oh, my God!
别动  别动
Stay still, stay still, stay still.
也许是外星人咬了你
Maybe you got bit by an alien.
所以联调局的人才会来
That would explain the FBI.
也许是变种人咬的
Or maybe a mutant bit you.
我成了超级英雄吗
Am I a superhero now?
宝贝
Baby.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
你说呢
What do you think I'm doing?
我总算有电影可拍了
I finally found my movie.
什么
What?
迈克尔  迈克尔不是你的素材
Michael? Michael is not your movie.
我们都不清楚他到底怎么了
We don't even know what happened to him.
正是这样
Exactly.
我要拍摄迈克尔的"前传"
I'm gonna get Michael's origin story on-camera.
你有点儿吓到我了
You're kind of creeping me out, man.
这儿没有超级英雄场面
Seriously, nothing superheroic to see here.
只是一块美味百吉饼
Just a delicious bagel.
伙计  我有个想法
Hey, man, I have this idea.
听来会很奇怪  但是别笑我
It's gonna sound really weird, but don't laugh, okay?
不敢保证
No promises.
我真的很想有你的能力
I, um...I really want to be able to do what you do.
所以我想我们再去一次那里
So I-I think maybe we could go back out there
让那东西咬我
and get that thing to bite me,
这样我们两个都能当超级英雄了
and then we could both be superheroes.
别说了  你开玩笑吧
Stop! What? Are you serious?
迈克尔  你可不能独占这好处
Michael, you can't keep this to yourself.
什么独占
Keep what to myself?
我们都不知道这是怎么回事
We don't even know what this thing is.
你居然还想要
Why the hell would you want it?
迈克尔  我不想再做猪仔了
Michael...I don't -- I don't want to be piggy anymore, man.
猪仔是书中最聪明的人物  却体格比较弱  备受欺凌
你不是的  伙计
You're -- you're not a pig, man.
布莱恩  听我说  你没什么不好的
Brian, listen to me. There's nothing wrong with you.
你只需要弄清自己想要什么
You've just got to figure out what it is you want
然后全力争取
and go after it.
相信我  你不想这样
I'm telling you -- you don't want this.
太对了  我不想变得超级强壮
Right, 'cause I don't want to be super-strong
或者能泡上妞儿...
or have a prayer of getting any ass this year or...
拜托  拜托了
Please, please.
不行  伙计
No, man!
不行
No.
-不开  -不开
- Not it. - Not it.
真幼稚
Children.
伙计们  伙计们  是联调局
Dudes, dudes, dudes. It's the FBI.
-什么  -联调局
- What? - It's the FBI.
宝贝  你在做什么
Baby, what are you doing?
-你好  -你们好
- Hi, there. - Hi.
罗斯特工和哈德森特工
Special agents Rose and Hudson.
我们想问几个问题
We wanted to ask you a few questions
关于几个街区外的那桩凶杀案
about the murder that occurred a few blocks from here.
首先  你认识被害人雅各布・卡特吗
First off, did you know the victim, Jacob Carter?
不  不太熟
Um, no, not really.
记得那天晚上有什么怪事发生吗
Do you remember anything unusual about that night?
我想没有
Not that I recall.
好  听说这附近有谁...
Right. Well, uh, heard about anyone in the neighborhood getting,
被咬伤吗
uh -- getting bit?
-配合一下  -我想没有
- Humor me. - No, I-I don't think so.
好  没关系  这样吧
All right. Well, no worries. How about this?
如果你听到什么奇怪的事
If you hear anything strange...
给我们打电话
Call us...
多晚都行
No matter how late.
-好的  -谢谢
- Okay. - Thanks.
谢谢
Thank you.
你怎么看
So, what do you think?
根据目前的线索来看
Well, based on what we've got so far,
可能又是个玛雅神
we could be dealing with another Mayan god.
这可真棒
Ah, that's fantastic,
上次轻松摆平嘛
'cause the other one was such a joy.
去学校宿舍看看吗
Campus dormitories?
好的
Yep.
联调局正在找咬你的东西
The FBI are looking for what bit you.
这是《X档案》那种事吗
Are you an "X-file"?
不  他才不是  听着
No. He's not an "X-file." Listen.
...来看  可能又是个玛雅神
...so far, we could be dealing with another Mayan god.
我是神了
I'm a golden god.
I am a golden god!
你们真可笑
You guys are ridiculous.
我是神了
I am a golden god.
我是个神
I am a god.
你们好
What's up, bvc?
我是斯考特・帕克
It's Scotty P.
正要跟我的伙计们
Patrolling with the oak hill crew --
道格  埃文和塔克一起巡逻
Doug...Evan...Tucker.
有个动物杀死了当地居民
See, some animal killed a local citizen,
所以我们今晚出动
so we're out here tonight
维护街道的安全
making sure these streets are safe
保护可爱的你们
for all you fine honeys out there, all right?
出发吧  小伙子们
Let's fan out, boys.
好的  出发
All right. Let's go.
走开  混蛋  今晚没心情
Back off, douche-wheel. Not tonight.
我好怕怕哦
Ooh. Oh. Ooh, I'm so scared.
听好了
Listen...
怎么回事
What...what the...?
我非抓住你不可  混蛋
Yeah, I got you now, you piece of...
有种像个男人一样滚出来单挑
Why don't you come take your beating like a man?
如果你不出来的话
If you won't come out and play,
我就去找你可爱的小女友
I'll go visit that little piece of yours.
叫凯特是吗
Kate?
我会去找她  让她见识下真正的男人
Yeah, I'll got visit Katie, show her what a real man --
迈克尔
Michael?
伙计  你以为这样很好玩吗
Dude, do you think this is funny?!
出来  别闹了
Come on! Cut it out.
可以问一个关于他的问题吗
Can I ask you something about him?
发生了这些事情
With everything that's happened,
你怕他吗
are you afraid of him?
起初  是的
At first, yeah.
这确实挺吓人的
I mean, it was pretty scary.
但后来  说实话
But...then, to be totally honest,
我觉得挺性感的
it's actually been pretty hot.
天啊
O...M...G.
宝贝
Baby?
你
Just...
你能告诉我们发生了什么吗
Can you tell us what happened?
我碰到了斯考特
I, uh -- I ran into Scott.
他追着我不放  然后我杀了他
He chased me, and I think I killed him.
什么
What?
关了
Turn it off.
Off!
他说起你来  然后我眼前一片红色
He started talking about you, and I saw red.
等我恢复意识  已经在往家跑了
The next thing I remember, I was running home.
录像里面
On the video...
你手上是什么东西
What were those things on your hands?
-爪子吗  -有没有人看到你
- Claws? - Did anybody see you?
凯特  你不是想替他找理由...
Kate, you're not trying to justify...
我们并不知道当时情况  布莱恩
No. We don't know what happened, Brian.
怎么  他就不能正当防卫吗
What? He can't defend himself?
东西给我
Give me this.
就猜到你们还会来
Figured I'd see you guys again.
要是你工作到位了
Well, if you did your job right,
我们也不用来了  不是吗
we wouldn't be here, would we?
别激动  什么情况
Easy. Uh, so, what do you got?
死者叫斯考特・帕克
Vic's name was Scott Parker.
看来杀死了卡特的东西再下杀手了
Looks like the same thing that killed the Carter kid got Mr. Parker here.
你说东西
Wait. Same thing?
我只是个地方警察
Look, I-I'm only the local yokel,
这孩子是被动物给撕碎的
but this kid was shredded by an animal.
他的心脏呢
Where's his heart?
巡警在那边找到了
Patrolman found it up the way there.
大部分被吃了
Eaten mostly.
带我们过去
Show us.
布莱恩  等等
Brian, wait.
你吃下了一颗人心吗
Did you eat a human heart?
-有没有  -你在说什么
- Did you? - What are you talking about?
他在说什么啊
What is he talking about?
斯考特死了
Scott's dead.
被人撕碎挖出了心脏
He was shredded, and his heart's gone.
那也未必是迈克尔干的
That doesn't mean that Michael --
那你以为怎么回事
What do you think happened to it?
他的心脏哪儿去了  迈克尔
Where's his heart, Michael?
-我不记得发生了什么  -别撒谎
- I don't remember what happened. - Don't lie to me!
布莱恩  冷静点
Hey, Brian, calm down!
肯定发生了一些我们不知道的事
Look, I mean, there's got to be an explanation for this.
是吗
Really?
他是正当防卫
It was...self-defense.
吃人心也叫正当防卫吗
Eating a heart is self-defense?
凯特  你想骗谁  我还是你自己
Kate, who are you trying to convince? Me or yourself?
离她远点
You need to back off.
怎么  你想把我的心也吃了吗
Why? You gonna eat my heart, too?
迈克尔
Michael!
我不知道我是怎么回事
I don't know what's happening to me.
我不知道我究竟是什么
I don't know who I am anymore.
你是迈克尔・惠勒
You're Michael Wheeler.
你是我的  听懂了吗
And you're mine, okay? You hear me?
我们要报警
We have to call the police.
布莱恩
Brian.
凯特  你怎么可以这样
Kate, how -- how can you?
你得看清现实啊
You have to see what's really going on here.
不管他是什么  都对你很不好
Whatever he is, it's not good -- it's not good for you.
迈克尔不是故意要伤害你的
Michael didn't mean to hurt you.
明显是故意的  凯特
Obviously he did, Kate.
你就是不懂  是吗
You just don't get it, do you?
我不懂什么
What? What don't I understand?
你从没爱过一个人
You've never been in love.
我们现在要找到答案
What we need are answers.
听不到他们讲话
I can't hear them.
凯特我们到底在干什么
Seriously, Kate, what are we doing?
干什么  你开玩笑吗
What are we doing? Seriously?
等等  凯特  别去
Wait. Kate, don't.
死者身上的爪痕很干净
Cut marks on both vics are clean
但从弯曲程度来看是动物爪子所致
but have the curvature of animal claws.
我也说不好
I don't know.
或许是四处游荡的野生动物
I mean, maybe there's a wild animal on the loose?
我们这儿最大的动物是浣熊
Biggest animal in the county is a raccoon.
-谢谢你的帮助  -不客气
- Thank you for your time. - You bet.
谢谢你  就这样
Appreciate it. Okay.
打听到什么了吗
So, what did I miss? Anything?
除非你想对浣熊发全境通告
Not unless you want to put an A.P.B. out on rocky raccoon.
好吧
Great.
网上没有当地警局的资料
Um, the local police files are not online,
我只好去查郡记录
so I had to dig through the county records.
十年前  有宗相似的悬案
Um, 10 years ago, there was a similar unsolved murder.
你看一下
Check it out.
致命伤由爪子造成  心脏被挖走
Death by claws and, uh, lack of heart?
那么这是
So we're talking a --
不是  当时还不到日子
No. Not that time of the month.
-太棒了  -是啊
- Awesome. - Yeah.
去查查资料  找点吃的
Time to hit the books and feed the monster.
他们肯定知道些东西
They know something.
我们要跟着他们
We got to follow them.
迈克尔  你听到了吗
Michael. Come on. Michael.
天啊
Geez.
你怎么找到我们的
How'd you find us?
手机里的全球定位系统
GPS in your phones.
废话
Duh.
伙计  你知道你有点吓着我了
You know, you're starting to creep me out, man.
彼此彼此  兄弟
The feeling's mutual, dude.
布莱恩  你还能黑进什么
What else can you hack into, Brian?
任何东西
Anything.
测试  测试  能听见吗
Test, test. Can you hear me?
收到
Copy that.
信号正在传入我的笔记本
Yeah, the feed is looping to my laptop right now.
进去  确保你坐得够近
Head in, make sure you're within spitting distance,
应该就没问题了
and we should be in business.
别被抓了
Um, and don't get arrested.
我去
I'll do it.
-你确定  -对  把包给我
- You sure? - Yeah. Give me the bag.
这样行吗
We good?
往左点
Uh...A little left.
这样呢
How's that?
太棒了  谢谢
Awesome. Thank you.
谢谢
Thanks.
老兄  两个汉堡
Dude, two burgers?
我都差不多一年没在这里吃饭了
Hey, I didn't eat at Big P's for like a year, okay?
眼睛雪亮  动脉阻塞
Clear eyes and clogged arteries --
绝对不能差啊
Can't lose.
看这个
Hey, check this out.
"被纯种头四代子孙所转化的狼人..."
"Werewolves that are turned up to four generations from pureblood..."
纯种是说始祖吗
Think he means Alpha?
"相对温和
"...are less feral
并且可以在任何时候变形"
and can transform before, during, and after the lunar cycle."
中了
Boom.
让我看看
Let me see that.
纯种的不会在变形过程中昏过去
Purebloods don't black out during the transformation.
他们可以控制自己
They can control themselves.
一些可以靠动物心脏生存
Some have been able to subsist off of animal hearts.
那么  什么情况
So... So, what?
我们在抓捕的是一只纯种的狼人吗
We're hunting a-a werewolf with a pedigree?
太棒了  希望他有证件
Awesome. Let's hope he has his papers.
是啊  希望银质物品可以杀死他
Yeah, and that silver can kill him.
那么
So...what?
他十年前在这里攻击了某个可怜的女人
Best in show comes here 10 years ago, ganked some poor woman.
然后尘埃落定  没有嫌疑了
Then when the dust settles and everything's in the clear,
就在这里住下了吗
he just sets up shop?
对  为心而来  为了女大学生而留下
Yeah, comes for the human hearts, stays for the co-eds.
好吧
Right.
之后一切安好
And then everything's wine and roses --
只吃动物心脏
And animal tickers --
直到他又渴望人类了
Until he gets the hankering for human again.
我就说这里有案子吧
Told you there was a case here.
现在我们只要找到它杀了它
Now we just got to find it and kill it.
我是狼人
I'm a werewolf.
狼人
A werewolf.
迈克尔  别这样
Michael, come on.
宝贝  你需要冷静下来
Baby, you need to calm down.
-冷静  我是个狼人  -我们需要找到
- Calm down? I'm a werewolf! - Hey, we need to find --
联调局的人想要杀死我
The FBI is trying to kill me.
闭嘴  都闭嘴
Shut up! Everybody, shut up, okay?
首先  这些人
First thing's first, those guys --
这些人不是联调局的  懂吗
Those guys aren't FBI, all right?
联调局的特工肯定不会老说"太棒了"
I'm pretty sure that FBI agents don't say "Awesome" that much.
还有
You know?
他们也绝对不会追杀大学生的
And -- and they definitely don't hunt and kill college kids.
他们还说了什么吗
Did -- did they say anything else?
老兄  他们就坐在那儿
Dude, they just sat and talked about
说什么他们分开一年了
how they have been apart for a year.
你之前说搭档基情什么  没准猜对了
You were probably right about that whole office-romance thing.
我完了
I'm screwed.
凯特  我们该怎么办
Kate, come on. What are we supposed to do?
行了  你知道吗
Okay, you know what?
你们  你们搞错重点了
You guys, you're missing the big picture, okay?
他们完全不知道你  迈克尔
They -- they don't know about you, Michael.
他们在找那个人  那个什么
They're looking for whoever, whatever
一开始咬你的  纯种
bit you in the first place, the pureblood.
那样
That...
那样我们就有时间
That gives us some time...
想办法
To figure it out, you know?
那你怎么打算的
So, what's the plan?
我余生就只吃鸡心吗
What, eat chicken hearts for the rest of my life?
迈克尔  宝贝
Michael. Baby.
喂  伙计们
Hey, guys.
我觉得我发现了什么
I think I found something.
布莱恩  离上班时间还早着呢
A little early for office hours, Brian.
你有什么事吗
What can I help you with?
我知道你是什么
I know what you are.
你在干什么
Hey. What are you doing?
天亮我们就走
We're leaving in the morning.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
那些人  他们可能找到迈克尔
Those guys -- look, they might find Michael, and --
不  凯特  你不用担心
No, Kate, you don't have to worry about that.
你什么都不用担心
You don't have to worry about anything.
我搞定了
I took care of it.
你搞定什么了
You took care of what?
布莱恩  你做了什么
Brian, what did you do?
我知道你是什么
I know what you are.
是啊  我是你的教授
Yeah, I'm your professor.
谢了  我一直在找那个呢
And thanks. I've been looking for that.
你在哪找到的
Where'd you find it?
你咬了我朋友之后  弄丢它的地方
Where you left it... after you bit my friend.
抱歉  你在说什...
I'm sorry. What are you --
打住打住  别想掩饰
Stop, stop, stop. Stop trying to cover.
认真听我说
Just listen to me very carefully.
我把这些都录下来了
I'm filming all this.
这里我也藏了摄像机
And I've got a hidden camera in here, too.
信号直接传回我家的笔记本里
It's feeding back to my laptop at home,
所以如果我发生了什么事
so if anything happens to me --
布莱恩  不会发生什么事的
Nothing is going to happen to you, Brian.
但是你得冷静点
But you know what? You need to calm down.
我要你把我变成狼人
I want you to turn me into a werewolf.
布莱恩  我不知道你从哪...
Brian, I-I don't know where you...
你不知道
You don't know?
真的吗
Really?
-不如我用这个划你一下  -布莱恩
- Well, how about I, uh, cut you with this. - Brian,
-听我说  -你知道这东西是银质的
- listen to me. - This thing's made of silver, you know.
听着  拜托  我不是你想的那样
Look, I'm not -- please, I'm not what you think that I am.
我不在乎你是什么  我只想你转化我
I don't care what you are. I just want you to turn me.
我不想伤害你
I don't want to hurt you.
你不会伤害我
You're not going to,
因为你伤害我  这些都会在CNN播出
'cause if you do, all of this winds up on CNN.
CNN: 美国有线电视新闻网络
你无意间撞见了卡特  变身  然后呢
So, you stumbled on Carter, wolfed out, and then what?
又开荤吃人心了吗
Got a taste for hearts again?
那种感觉忘不掉
You never lose the taste,
如果你傻到会吃一次的话
if you're stupid enough to have one.
一旦吃过人心
Once you have a human heart,
几乎就无法控制住体内的兽性
it's almost impossible to control the monster inside.
但是我做到了  直到上周我...
But I did, until last week when I, uh...
像俗话说的那样  旧瘾复发
Fell off the wagon, as they say.
你根本不知道  这有多艰难
You have no idea -- no idea -- how hard it is.
我一直努力不让自己伤害别人
I've trained myself not to hurt anyone.
我一直努力让自己
I have -- I have trained myself to...
强咽下其他心脏
choke down those other hearts.
动物心脏
Animal hearts.
我一直都没伤人
And I'v been clean.
直到上周
Until last week?
我看到卡特一个人  他...
And then I saw Carter alone, and he was...
他看起来很虚弱
He looked so weak.
现在不那么容易掩盖这些事了
It's harder to cover things up nowadays.
我知道猎人迟早会发现的
I knew a hunter would catch wind of this sooner or later.
是的  他们来了
They did. They're here.
你需要一个替罪羊
You needed a patsy.
迈克尔
Michael.
是的
Yes.
那个总在我课上睡觉的年轻人
The young man who sleeps through most of my lectures.
谁会想他呢
I mean, who would miss him?
我
Me.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
我想要看到你们看到的一切
I want to see what you guys see...
做你们能做的事
do what you do.
我不想再当猪仔了
I'm sick of being piggy.
雷尔夫是小说中正面的领袖人物
我想当雷尔夫
I want to be Ralph.
我们选择不了自己的身份
We don't get to choose who we are.
我做到了
I did.
-天呐  -布莱恩
- Oh, my god. - Brian.
-天呐  -你疯了吗
- Oh, my god. - What are you? Insane?
我救了你们一命  不客气
You're welcome for saving your ass.
你们看
Look, watch.
谢谢
Thank you.
我还从没杀过纯种狼人
I've never killed a pureblood before.
他刚刚在看什么
What was he looking at?
搞什么名堂
What the hell?
看见了
See?
后患已除
Problem solved.
他们杀了那个纯种的  就不会继续查了
They killed the pureblood, they're moving on,
就像你说的  我们没了后顾之忧
and we're in the clear, just like you said.
我从来没说
I never said --
凯特  我
Kate, I, uh...
我这么做是为了保护你
I did this to protect you.
你办不到的事我办到了
I did what you couldn't.
他们看见摄像机了  布莱恩
They saw the camera, Brian.
你觉得他们不会查到你头上来吗
You don't think they'll trace that back to you?
你有什么毛病
What the hell's wrong with you?
我没毛病
Nothing's wrong with me.
这是你说的
You told me that.
我只是终于弄清了我想要什么
I just...finally figured out what I want,
我现在要努力争取了
and now I'm going after it.
你以为我一直躲在摄像机后吗
You thought I was hiding behind this?
我一直躲在你的身后
I was hiding behind you.
我受够了活在你的阴影之下
I am done living in your shadow.
我总摆脱不掉你的阴影
I've always lived in your shadow.
但是现在  我们旗鼓相当了
But now -- now we're equals.
你能做到的我都行  不是吗
Anything you can do, right?
怎么  你以为这是比赛吗
What? You think this is a game?
你知道你对自己做了什么吗
Do you have any idea what you've done to yourself?
既然你不肯咬我  我只好
Well, you wouldn't bite me, so I had to...
你让他咬你
You asked him to?
他求你咬他
He asked you to bite him?
我没同意  好吗
I didn't, okay?
我不想伤害你
I didn't want to hurt you.
我绝不会伤害你  布莱恩
I would never hurt you, Brian.
我体内的这个恶魔  你不想这样
This thing inside of me -- you don't want this.
现在说这话已经太迟了
Oh, well, it's too late for that now.
我记得袭击斯考特的那一刻
I remember attacking Scott.
我记得把他跳动的心从他胸膛里掏出来
I remember ripping his beating heart out of his chest.
我记得我咬那颗心时
I remember the look in his dead eyes
他已无生气的眼睛里的眼神  布莱恩
when I bit into that heart, Brian.
最重要的是  我记得那味道有多美
And above all, I remember how sweet,
多好吃  自从我吃了心脏
how delicious it tasted, and ever since I've tasted it,
我觉得更强大  也更失控了
I've felt more powerful and more out of control.
是更脆弱
More weak.
你不需要像迈克尔这样的人
You don't need someone like Michael.
你需要一个能照顾你的人
You need someone that can take care of you.
我能照顾自己
I can take care of myself.
放了她
Let her go.
不然呢  你要哭吗
Or what? You gonna cry some more?
不  不要
No! No! No!
神  神
God! God!
去死吧神
God!
宝贝  宝贝
Oh, baby. Oh, baby.
求你别死
Please don't die.
别死  千万别死
Please don't die. Please don't die.
我爱你  宝贝
I love you, baby.
我爱你
I love you.
迈克尔
Michael?
Michael!
凯特  听我说
Kate, listen to me.
我爱你  我爱你
I love you. I love you.
你会理解的  你只要看到我所见到的
You'll understand. You just need to see what I see.
等我咬了你  你就明白了
After I bite you, you'll understand.
凯特
Kate?
让我进来
Let me in.
对不起  我不想故意吓唬你
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
我们能弥补这一切
We can fix this. We can...
你就让我进来吧  好吗
just let me in, okay?
布莱恩
Brian?
布莱恩  我出来了
Brian, I'm coming out.
我现在明白了
I see it now.
我懂了
I understand.
我说过会没事的
I told you it would be all right.
是啊
Yeah.
会没事的  给
It will be. Here.
不  不要
No, no!
我完成布莱恩的电影不是为了辩解
I didn't finish Brian's movie to justify what happened.
不瞒你们说
To be totally honest,
我都不知道我是不是真的明白发生了什么
I'm not really even sure if I understand it at all.
我只想让你们知道
I just wanted you to know that --
迈克尔并不是个彻头彻尾的怪物
that Michael wasn't always a monster.
我们几个都不是
None of us were.
五年之后
Five years from now?
希望能够通过律师资格考试  做个律师
Hopefully passed the bar exam, practicing law.
不去大公司干  而是环保事业之类的
Nothing corporate, something green, you know?
天呐
Oh, geez.
或许去HBO工作
Uh, maybe, like, working for HBO
或者像迈克尔・摩尔那样
or -- or, like, Michael Moore.
那样不错
That'd be cool.
我要乘船在海上航行
I will be on a boat in the middle of the ocean
我美丽的女友也会伴我左右
with my beautiful girl by my side.
我会离开
I'm leaving.
你们再也不会见到我
And you'll never hear from me ever again.
我知道还有其他的出路
Look, I know that there's another way.
我可以吃动物的心脏
I can eat animal hearts.
我绝不会伤害任何人
I've never hurt anyone.
反正不会伤害人类
Nobody human, anyway.
我不是自愿变成这样
I didn't choose this.
求你们了
Please...
请给我一次机会
Please give me a chance.
那么
Okay, so, uh...
这位  嗯
- ...this - - Yeah --
是迈克尔  所以那位就是
is Michael, which means that that is...
布莱恩・威尔科特斯
Brian Wilcox,
友善的摄影师邻居
our friendly neighborhood cameraman.
正确
Right.
好吧
All right, so...
那么  她比我们早差不多半天
What, she's got about a half-day jump on us?
你没事吧
You all right?
凯特说得对
Look, Kate's right.
她没伤害任何人  至少没伤害人类
She hasn't hurt anybody -- well, anybody human at least.
而且这也不是她自愿的
No, she didn't -- she didn't choose this.
我们就给她一次机会吧
Let's give her a shot.
你当真
Seriously?
是的
Yeah, yeah.
假如凯特再出现
And, look, if Kate pops back up,
假如她犯了错
I mean, if she strays,
那么毫无疑问
then no questions asked.
我们就做该做的事  杀了她
We do what we got to do and, um, we take her down.
萨姆
Hey, Sam?
怎么了
Yeah?
我真的总说"太棒了"吗
Do I really say "Awesome" a lot?
不  不  没有
No. No, no. No.
太棒了
Awesome.
最近还好吗*
*...with you lately?
你还好吗*
*What's the matter?
你最近还好吗*
*What's the matter with you lately?
歌曲: What's the Matter
歌手: Milo Greene
寻梦人  你会蹉跎岁月*
*Dreamer, you will waste your time.
你是否想过为什么我们一直徘徊*
*Do you ever wonder why we go on and on and on?
而爱早没了踪影*
*Love is gone and gone and gone.
你还好吗*
*What's the matter?
你最近还好吗*
*What's the matter with you lately?